azmagento.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy

**Personal information collection**

 **magenshop.com** may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

\- Information about transactions carried out over this website;  
\- Any other information that you send to magenshop.com.

  **Using personal information**

 **magenshop.com may use your personal information to:**

\- Administer this website;  
\- Collect payments from you;  
\- Send to you products that you purchase;  
\- Email you information regarding the products.

Where magenshop.com discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, magenshop.com may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

  **Securing your data**

magenshop.com will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

  **Cross-border data transfers**

Information that magenshop.com collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which magenshop.com operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

  **Updating this statement**

magenshop.com may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

  **Other websites**

This website contains links to other websites. magenshop.com is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.
